<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gzs.fyi</title>
    <link>https://gzs.fyi/</link>
    <description>Recent content on gzs.fyi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gzs.fyi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gzs.fyi/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gzs.fyi/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a developer advocate with a passion for getting people of all experience levels involved with technology and development with new resources. I focus on building personal connections between users to share stories and experiences. I have a particular love for open source technologies, creating readable documentation, and making the whole ecosystem more enjoyable, welcoming place to be a part of.
Outside of technology, I can be found curating the perfect Spotify playlists, finding the best new restaurants in town, and perfecting my skincare routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://gzs.fyi/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gzs.fyi/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Here is a list of some of the projects I have worked on as a Developer Advocate.
Sample Apps  Amazon Review Scraper Okta Twilio Demo Pridebot SIGNAL 2019 Raffle Slack Portal Slack new user notifications Slack actions and dialog Slack Smartsheet Helpdesk  Blog Posts  Using a Slack app as a communication portal between different workspaces Creating an API from HTML: Scraping Amazon Reviews into Google Sheets Exploring new user notifications in Slack PrideBot is a reminder that pride is both worldwide and never-ending 🏳️‍🌈  Talks  Making the most of Slack webhooks (Slack Platform Community) &amp;ndash; Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>